<# 
Alphabetizing links can be tedious.  
Many pages have alphabetized link banners along the bottom, and Write-Link can make these very easy.  
By providing a table to Write-Link, the links are neatly alphabetized.  
By providing the -Horizontal switch, the links are displayed horizontally
By providing the -HorizontalSeparator parameter, the separator is changed from the default (|) to a *

-SortedLinkTable defaults to position 0, so you don't have to spell out the whole name
#>        
Write-Link @{
    'Privacy Statement' = "Privacy.aspx"
    'Contact Us' = "ContactUs.aspx"
    'Terms Of Use' = "Terms.aspx"
    'Trademarks' = "Trademarks.aspx"
} -Horizontal    
